# Jason Hannanto

#### WEB/SOFTWARE ENGINEER · STUDENT

3001 Front St. Alhambra, CA 91803

□ (626) 267-6038 | Mannanto@usc.edu | Manuel Manue

## Summary\_

Hi! My name is Jason. I'm currently a sophomore at the University of Southern California pursuing a B.S in Computer Science. Creating and perfecting a smooth and exciting user experience on a digital platform is my craft and I'm always excited to learn about new technologies to see how I better develop solutions. I know I have a long ways to go, as well as a lot to learn, which is why I am working hard everyday to achieve my dreams

## **Education**

#### **University Of Southern California**

Los Angeles, CA

Intended Degree: B.S. in Computer Science Expected Graduation: 2020

**Pasadena City College** 

Pasadena, CA

2015-2017

COMPUTER SCIENCE

## Work Experience

#### **USC Davis School of Gerontology**

Los Angeles, CA

Webmaster Aug 2017 - Present

- Management of online websites, content, and courses.
- HTML, CSS, Wordpress, Blackboard

#### **Reliant Pulmonary/Critical Care**

Monterey Park, CA

MEDICAL SCRIBE

Mar. 2016 - Aug 2017

- Complete realtime/retrospective charting of patient encounters, including History of Present Illness, Review of Systems, Past Medical History, Family/Social History, Assessment (ICD-10 coding)/Plan, Vitals, Diagnostic Tests, and Medications.
- Navigation/set-up of EHR/Radiographic Imaging software/programs
- Documentation/Transcription of Lab Results, Radiographic Imagery Reports, and procedural reports.

## **Projects**

#### [Current] Music Lyric/Chord Management Web App

WEB APP ALLOWS USERS TO CREATE/STORE SONGS WITH CHORDS FOR LIVE PLAYING. FEATURES THE CAPABILITY TO TRANSPOSE

Aug 2017 - Present

- **KEYS LIVE. USED WEEKLY BY THE CHURCH MUSIC TEAM.** Working under a Senior Software Developer
- Debug posted issues / Refactor code for efficiency
- Develop new features for Web App

#### [Current] JasonHannanto.github.io

PORTFOLIO/RESUME WEBSITE Aug 2017 - Present

• Creating a visually appealing and responsive website

### Skills\_

Frontend, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Backend, Node.js, Express.js

Database, NoSQL, MongoDB, Mongoose

Programming, C++, Python

Version Control, Git

Principles, REST, TDD, OPP, Unit Testing